S.GHUFRAN NADEEM

User Interface Developer. Assistan Manager at Axact



Name: Syed Ghufran Nadeem Nationality : Pakistan ID Number: 42101-1890160-3



Personal Profile

Highly Creative and versatile web developer who worships updated tools. I have multitude of experience in the field of corporate identity Web designing and User Interface Developer. I connect abstraction to UI development Worked with renowned and multi-national firms in karachi pakistan



Skills



> 828 Tech

http://828getsresults.com/ Tools & Technology: Wordpress, Jupiter, Xhtml, Css2, Css3, Jquery

Pacific Surgical

http://www.pacificsurgicalwa.com/ Tools & Technology: Wordpress, Cumstom Design, Xhtml, Css3, Jquery

Blue Digital Avenue

https://www.bluedigitalavenue.com Tools & Technology: Xhtml, Css3, Jquery, Custom Jquery, Bootstrap

> Content Devs

http://www.contentdevs.com/ Tools & Technology: Custom Jquery, Bootstrap, Xhtml, Css3, Jquery

Pixels Logo Design

http://www.pixelslogodesign.com/ Tools & Technology: Custom Jquery, Bootstrap, Xhtml, Css3, Jquery



+92 334 325 0574



ghufrannadeem82@gmail.com



ghufrannadeem.com



EDUCATION

KARACHI UNIVERSITY 2008 - 2011 B.Com - Commerce Major Subject

- Accounts
- Mathamatic
- English
- Business of Commerce

- GOV. DEGREE COLLAGE N.KARACHI 2003 2005
 I.Com Commerce
 Major Subject
 - Accounts
 - Mathamatic
 - English
 - Islamiat

MATRICULATION 2008 - 2011 Biology

Major Subject

- Biology
- Physics
- Chemistry
- Methamatic

COMPUTER QUALIFICATINO

Web Engineering 2007
 M.S Office 2002
 Computer Hardware 2002
 CIT 2005



WORK EXPERIENCE



AXACT

Jan 2017 - Dec 2018 Asst Manager & Senoir UI Dev.

Responsibilities:

Manage Project deadline project lineup with other projects. Fullfill requirment from client.
Custom Jquery Objects, Html5 Css3, Cross Browser Compatibility, W3C Varified Css and Html, Css based Layout, Jquery Objects Customization and Implementations, Bootstrap.



ITCONCEPT

Mar 2016 - Jan 2017 Manager of UI Development Team

Responsibilities:

Manage team work and there projects within in clients deadline using Custom Jquery Objects, Html5 Css3, Cross Browser Compatibility, W3C Varified Css and Html, Css based Layout, Jquery Objects Customization and Implementations, Bootstrap.



INFORMATIQUE

June 2015 - Mar 2016 Sr. User Interface Dev

Responsibilities:

Custom Jquery Objects, Html5 Css3, Cross Browser Compatibility, W3C Varified Css and Html, Css based Layout, Jquery Objects Customization and Implementations, Bootstrap.



ICT AXACT

Oct 2013 - Jun 2015 Userinterface Developer

Responsibilities:

Html5 Css3, Cross Browser Compatibility, W3C Varified Css and Html, Css based Layout, Jquery Objects Customization and Implementations, Bootstrap.



Responsibilities:

User Interface Dev

Html5 Css3, Cross Browser Compatibility, W3C Varified Css and Html, Css based Layout, Jquery implementation



INFORMATIQUE

July 2009 - April 2013 Sr. User Interface Dev

Responsibilities:

Jquery Implementations, Html5 Css3, Cross Browser Compatibility, W3C Varified Css and Html, Css based Layout, Jquery.